Guide to the W. D. Davies papers, 1911-2007 UA.29.02.0016
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA2014.0065, 1911-2007; 2
  - Books, 5
    - The Bible Today (25:1966) (Box 67)
      Author: Unknown; Publisher: North Central Publishing Company; Place of Publication: St Cloud; Paperback; Language: English; Number twenty-five; Significance to W.D. Davies: Contributor
    - Biblia Hebraica, 1925 (Box 64)
      Author: Edited by Rud. Kittel; Place of Publication: Stuttgart; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Annotated
    - Biblia Hebraica Edidit Rudkittel II, 1925 (Box 71)
      Author: Rud. Kittel (Ed); Place of Publication: Stuttgart; Hardcover; Language: Hebrew
    - Blodeuglwm o Englynion, undated (Box 72)
      Author: W.J. Gruffydd; Publisher: William Lewis A'i Gwmni; Place of Publication: Cardiff; Paperback; Language: Welsh
    - The Book of Common Prayer, 1977 (Box 75)
      Publisher: Church Hymnal Corporation and The Seabury Press; Place of Publication: New York; Hardcover; Language: English
    - British Academy Directory, 1992-1993, 1995-1996, 2000-2001 (Box 76)
      Publisher: Seacourt Press; Place of Publication: Oxford; Paperback; Language: English
    - The Cambridge History of Judaism: Volume 1, 1984 (Box 67)
      Author: W.D. Davies and Louis Finkelstein; Publisher: Cambridge University Press; Place of Publication: Cambridge; Hardcover; Language: English; Volume 1 of 3; Significance to W.D. Davies: Co-editor
    - The Cambridge History of Judaism: Volume 2, 1989 (Box 67)
      Author: W.D. Davies and Louis Finkelstein; Publisher: Cambridge University Press; Place of Publication: Cambridge; Hardcover; Language: English; Volume 2 of 3; Significance to W.D. Davies: Co-editor
    - The Cambridge History of Judaism: Volume 3, 1999 (Box 67)
      Author: William Horbury, W.D. Davies, John Sturdy; Publisher: Cambridge University Press; Place of Publication: Cambridge; Hardcover; Language: English; Volume 3 of 3; Significance to W.D. Davies: Co-editor
    - Caneuon (Box 72)
      Author: Volander Jones; Paperback; Language: Welsh
    - Caneuon Amanwy, 1956 (Box 69)
      Author: David Rees Griffiths; Publisher: Gomer Press; Place of Publication: Llandysul; Hardcover; Language: Welsh; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Caniadu (Box 69)
      Author: John Morris Jones; Hardcover; Language: Welsh; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Canu'r Pwll a'r Pulpud, 1987 (Box 69)
      Author: Huw Walters; Publisher: Gee Press; Hardcover; Language: Welsh; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Capire il Sermone sul monte: il quadro storico, teologico e culturale, 1975 (Box 62)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: Cambridge University Press; Place of Publication: London; Paperback; Language: Italian; translated by Editrice Claudiana; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - Cerddi Cadwgan, 1953 (Box 72)
      Author: D.R. Griffiths, Pennar Davies, Gareth Alban Davies, Rhydwen Williams, J. Gwyn Griffiths, Gwasg Gadwgan; Publisher: Gadwgan Press; Paperback; Language: Welsh
    - Cerddi'r Caeaf, 1952 (Box 69)
      Author: R. Williams Parry; Publisher: Gee Press; Hardcover; Language: Welsh; First Edition; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Cerddi'r Lleiafrif, 1932 (Box 72)
      Author: Tom Parry; Publisher: Gwasg Aberystwyth; Paperback; Language: Welsh
    - The Christ and the Faiths, 1986 (Box 73)
      Author: Kenneth Cragg; Publisher: Westminster Press; Place of Publication: Philadelphia; Paperback; Language: English
    - Christian Engagements with Judaism, 1999 (Box 63)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: Trinity Press International; Place of Publication: Harrisburg, Pennsylvania; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - Christian Origins, 1985 (Box 70)
      Author: Christopher Rowland; Publisher: S.P.C.K. London; Place of Publication: Great Britain; Paperback; Language: English
    - Christian Origins and Judaism, 1973 (Box 63)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: Arno Press; Hardcover; Language: English; Part of The Jewish People: History, Religion, Literature; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - Christian Origins and Judaism: A Collection of New Testament Studies, 1962 (Box 63)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: Darton, Longman and Todd LTD; Place of Publication: London; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - Christians Among Jews and Gentiles, 1986 (Box 65)
      Author: Edited by George W.E. Nickelsburg with George W. MacRae; Publisher: Fortress Press; Place of Publication: Philadelphia; Paperback; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Contributor
    - Church Services: The United Church of England and Ireland (Box 74)
      Language: English
    - Chwalu Cnapau, 1968 (Box 69)
      Author: Vivian Jones; Publisher: Gomer Press; Place of Publication: Llandysul; Hardcover; Language: Welsh
    - The Climax of the Covenant: Christ and the Law in Pauline Theology, 1991 (Box 70)
      Author: Unknown; Publisher: Fortress Press; Place of Publication: Minneapolis; Paperback; Language: English
    - Coming to Terms: A Study in Memory and History, 1987 (Box 68)
      Author: Henry F. May; Publisher: University of California Press; Place of Publication: Berkeley; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - A Community Built on Words: The Constitution in History and Politics (Box 66)
      Author: H. Jefferson Powell; Language:; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription, Dedication
    - A Companion to Greek Studies, 1931 (Box 64)
      Author: Leonard Whibley; Publisher: Cambridge University Press; Place of Publication: Cambridge; Hardcover; Language: English; Fourth edition; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription, Annotated
    - A Complete Concordance to the Old and New Testament of the Apocrypha (Box 73)
      Author: Alexander Cruden; Publisher: Frederick Warren & CO; Place of Publication: New York; Hardcover; Language: English
    - Congregational Church Hymnal (Box 73)
      Author: George S. Barrett; Publisher: Novello & Co LTD; Place of Publication: London; Hardcover; Language: English
    - Conservative Judaism: Volume XXV 1971 (Box 74)
      Author: Unknown; Language: English
    - Crossroads: Essays on Catholic Novelists, 1982 (Box 68)
      Author: Albert Sonnenfeld; Publisher: French :Literature Publications Company; Place of Publication: South Carolina; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Annotated
    - Crwydro Sir Gar, 1955 (Box 72)
      Author: Aneirin Talfan Davies; Publisher: Llyfrau'r Dryw; Place of Publication: Llandybie, Wales; Hardcover; Language: Welsh
    - Cudd Fy Meiau, 1998 (Box 72)
      Author: Pennar Davies; Publisher: John Penri Press; Place of Publication: Swansea; Paperback; Language: Welsh
    - Curig, 1992 (Box 72)
      Author: Huw Ethall; Publisher: John Perry Press; Place of Publication: Swansea; Paperback; Language: Welsh; First Edition
    - Cwm Aman, 1996 (Box 72)
      Author: Hywel Teifi Edwards; Publisher: Gomer Press; Place of Publication: Llandysul; Paperback; Language: Welsh
    - Cyfansoddiadau a Beirdniadaethau (1970) (Box 69)
      Author: J. Tysul Jones; Publisher: Gomer Press; Place of Publication: Llandysul; Paperback; Language: Welsh; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Cyfansoddiadau a Beirdniadaethau (1974) (Box 72)
      Author: Stephen J. Williams; Paperback; Language: Welsh
    - Cyfansoddiadau A Beirnaiadaethau (1969) (Box 72)
      Author: J. Tysul Jones; Publisher: Gomer Press; Language: Welsh
    - Cyrmry Patagonia, 1942 (Box 72)
      Author: R. Bryn Williams; Publisher: Aberystwyth Press; Place of Publication: Llandysul; Hardcover; Language: Welsh
    - Dail Pren, 1957 (Box 69)
      Author: Waldo Williams; Publisher: Aberystwyth Press; Place of Publication: Llandysul; Hardcover; Language: Welsh; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Dei Entstehung des Weihnachtsfestes (Box 66)
      Author: Oscar Cullmann; Language: German; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Die Berg Predigt, 1970 (Box 62)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: Cambridge University Press; Place of Publication: London; Paperback; Language: German; translated by Claudius Verlag Munchen; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - Dilyn Llwybrau, 1967 (Box 69)
      Author: T.I. Ellis; Publisher: Merlin Press; Place of Publication: Sir Gaerfryrddin; Hardcover; Language: Welsh; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Diwinyddiath, 1995 (Box 72)
      Author: Unknown; Paperback; Language: Welsh
    - Donum Gentillicium: New Testament Studies in honour of David Daube, 1978 (Box 65)
      Author: Co-edited by C.K. Barrett, E. Bammell and W.D. Davies; Publisher: Oxford Press; Place of Publication: Oxford; Hardcover; Language: English/German; Significance to W.D. Davies: Co-editor
    - The Duke Divinity School Review, Fall 1981 (Box 67)
      Author: Thomas. A Langford (Ed); Publisher: Divinity School, Duke University; Place of Publication: Durham, North Carolina; Paperback; Language: English; Volume 46 number 1; Significance to W.D. Davies: Contributor of text of speech given on his retirement from Duke Divinity School.
    - Dying for God: Martyrdom and the Making of Christianity and Judaism (Box 74)
      Author: Daniel Boyarin; Language: English
    - Early Christian Thought in its Jewish Context, 1996 (Box 70)
      Author: John Barclay and John Sweet; Publisher: Cambridge University Press; Place of Publication: Great Britain; Hardcover; Language: English
    - Early Christianity according to the Traditions in Acts, 1987 (Box 73)
      Author: Gerd Ludemann; Publisher: Fortress Press; Place of Publication: Minneapolis; Paperback; Language: English
    - Ecumenical Dialogue at Harvard: the Roman Catholic-Protestant Colloquium, 1964 (Box 67)
      Author: Samuel H. Miller and G. Ernest Wright (Editors); Publisher: Belknap Press of Harvard University Press; Place of Publication: Cambridge, MA; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Contributor
    - The Education of the Christian Faith (Box 74)
      Author: Kenneth Cragg; Language: English
    - Efrydiau Beiblaidd Bangor, 1978 (Box 69)
      Author: Cyfrol Deyrnged and Isaac Thomas; Publisher: John Penri Press; Place of Publication: Abertawe; Hardcover; Language: Welsh; Significance to W.D. Davies: Contributor
    - El Sermon De La Montana, 1975 (Box 62)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Place of Publication: Madrid; Paperback; Language: Spanish; translated by A. De La Fuente Adanez; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - Elfed, 1957 (Box 69)
      Author: Emlyn G. Jenkins; Publisher: Aberystwyth Press; Place of Publication: Llandysul; Hardcover; Language: Welsh; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Elfennau Barddoniaeth, 1936 (Box 72)
      Author: T. H. Parry-Williams; Publisher:; Place of Publication: Cardiff; Hardcover; Language: Welsh; Second Edition
    - Erwau'r Glo, 1976 (Box 72)
      Author: Huw Walters; Publisher: Salisbury Press; Place of Publication: Swansea; Paperback; Language: Welsh
    - Esther, 1995 (Box 74)
      Author: David Daube; Publisher: The Oxford Centre for Postgraduate Hebrew Studies; Place of Publication: Oxford, England; Paperback; Language: English
    - Everyman's Talmud, 1932 (Box 64)
      Author: A. Cohen; Publisher: The Temple Press; Place of Publication: London; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription, Annotated
    - Exploring the Gospel of John, 1996 (Box 65)
      Author: Edited by R. Alan Culpepper and C. Clifton Black; Place of Publication: Westminster John Knox Press; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Contributor
    - Final Account: Paul's Letter to the Romans, 1995 (Box 66)
      Author: Krister Stendahl; Publisher: Fortress Press; Place of Publication: Minneapolis; paperback; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - The Fourth Gospel, 1953 (Box 64)
      Author: C.H. Dodd; Publisher: Cambridge University Press; Place of Publication: Great Britain; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Annotated
    - From Alienation to At-One-Ness, 1977 (Box 67)
      Author: Francis A. Eigo; Publisher: The Villanova University Press; Place of Publication: Villanova, Pennsylvania; Paperback; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Contributor
    - From Schweitzer to Scholem: Reflections of Sabbatai Svi (Box 68)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - From Text to Tradition: A History of the Second Temple and Rabbinic Judaism, 1991 (Box 71)
      Author: Unknown; Publisher: Ktav Publishing House; Place of Publication: New Jersey; Paperback; Language: English
    - The Glory of Christ in the New Testament, 1987 (Box 65)
      Author: Edited by L.D. Hurst and N.T. Wright; Publisher: Clarendon Press; Place of Publication: New York; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Contributor
    - Goronwy'r Alltud, 1947 (Box 69)
      Author: Glad Rhyddallt; Publisher: Brython Press; Place of Publication: Chwefror; Hardcover; Language: Welsh; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - The Gospel According to Saint Matthew, 1988 (Box 63)
      Author: W.D. Davies and Dale Allison Jr.; Publisher: T&T Clark Limited; Place of Publication: Edinburgh; Hardcover; Language: English; Volume 1 of 3; Significance to W.D. Davies: Co-authored
    - The Gospel and the Land, 1994 (Box 62)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: JSOT Press; Place of Publication: Sheffield, England; Paperback; Language: English; Biblical Seminar 25, reprint of 1974; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - The Gospel and the Land, 1974 (Box 63)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: University of California Press; Place of Publication: Berkeley and Los Angeles; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - The Gospel and the Land: Early Christianity and Jewish Territorial Doctrine, 1974 (Box 62)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: University of California Press; Place of Publication: Berkeley and Los Angeles; Hardcover; Language: English; Published in association with Catherine and Lady James Grace foundation of Wales; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - The Gospel and the Land: Early Christianity and Jewish Territorial Doctrine, 1974 (Box 63)
    - The Gospel and the Sacred, 1994 (Box 73)
      Author: Robert G. Hammerton-Kelly; Publisher: Fortress Press; Place of Publication: Minneapolis; Paperback; Language: English
    - The Gospel of John & Judaism, 1975 (Box 68)
      Author: C.K. Barrett; Publisher: S.P.C.K. London; Place of Publication: London; Paperback; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Gramadeg Cymraeg, 1946 (Box 72)
      Author: J.J. Evans; Publisher: Aberystwyth Press; Place of Publication: Llandysul; Hardcover; Language: Welsh
    - Great Religions of the World, 1971 (Box 67)
      Author: National Geographic Society; Publisher: National Geographic Society; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Contributor
    - Greek Grammar, 1929 (Box 64)
      Author: E.A. Sonnenschein; Publisher: Aberdeen University Press; Place of Publication: Aberdeen; Hardcover; Language: English; Thirteenth edition; Significance to W.D. Davies: Annotated
    - The Greek New Testament, 1964 (Box 71)
      Author: R.V.G. Tasker; Publisher: Oxford University Press; Place of Publication: Great Britain; Hardcover; Language: Greek
    - A Greek-English Lexicon of the New Testament: And Other Early Christian Literature, 1977 (Box 71)
      Author: W.J. Hickie; Publisher: Baker Book House; Place of Publication: Michigan; Paperback; Language: English
    - Greek-English Lexicon to the New Testament, 1957 (Box 71)
      Author: William F. Arndt & F. Wilbur Gingrich; Publisher: University of Chicago Press; Place of Publication: Illinois; Hardcover; Language: English
    - Grey Eminence: A Study in Religion and Politics, 1941 (Box 68)
      Author: Aldous Huxley; Publisher: Chatto & Windus; Place of Publication: London; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Grym Y Lli, 1969 (Box 72)
      Author: Emyr Jones; Publisher: Gomer Press; Place of Publication: Llandysul; Hardcover; Language: Welsh; First edition
    - Gwenallt: Bardd Crefyddol, 1974 (Box 72)
      Author: J.E. Meredith; Publisher: Gomer Press; Place of Publication: Llandysul; Hardcover; Language: Welsh; First Edition
    - Gwyr Llen, 1948 (Box 69)
      Author: Aneirin Talfan Davies; Publisher: W. Griffiths A'I Frodyr; Place of publication: London; Hardcover; Language: Welsh; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Gyda Gwawr Y Bore, 1970 (Box 72)
      Author: Aneirin Talfan Davies; Publisher: Merlin Press; Place of Publication: Sir Gaerfryrddin; Hardcover; Language: Welsh; First Edition
    - Hanes Cymru YN Y Bedwaredd Ganrif Ar Bymtheg, 1933 (Box 72)
      Author: R.T. Jenkins; Publisher: Wales University Press; Place of Publication: Cardiff; Hardcover; Language: Welsh
    - Hastings Law Journal, 1978 (Box 67)
      Author: Pamela Carder Fletcher (Ed); Place of Publication: San Francisco; Paperback; Language: English; Volume 29 Number 6; Significance to W.D. Davies: Contributor
    - A Hebrew and English Lexicon of the Old Testament (Box 74)
      Author: Edward Robinson; Language: English
    - Historical Sites in Israel (Box 75)
      Author: Moshe Pearlman and Yaacov Yannai; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - A History of Greek Philosophy: Volume Four, 1975 (Box 71)
      Author: W.K.C. Guthrie; Publisher: Cambridge University Press; Place of Publication: New York; Hardcover; Language: English
    - A History of Greek Philosophy: Volume Six, 1981 (Box 71)
    - A History of the Christian Church, 1918 (Box 64)
      Author: Willston Walker; Publisher: Scribner Press; Place of Publication: Edinburgh; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Annotated/Inscription
    - History of New Testament Research: Volume One, 1992 (Box 70)
      Author: William Baird; Publisher: Fortress Press; Place of Publication: Minneapolis; Hardcover; Language: English
    - Hostage Bound Hostage Free, 1987 (Box 66)
      Author: Ben and Carol Weir; Publisher: The Westminster Press; Place of Publication: Philadelphia; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - I am He, 2000 (Box 75)
      Author: Catrin H. Williams; Publisher: J. C. B. Mohr; Place of Publication: Tubingen; Hardcover; Language: English
    - I Asked for Wonder: A Spiritual Anthology of Abraham Joshua Heschel (Box 66)
      Author: Samuel H. Dresner; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - The Insecurity of Freedom: Essays on Human Existence (Box 74)
      Author: Abraham J. Heschel; Language: English
    - Intergerini Parietis Septvm, 1981 (Box 67)
      Author: Dikran Y. Hadidian; Publisher: The Pickwick Press; Place of Publication: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania; Paperback; Language: Multiple Languages; Pittsburgh Theological Monograph series number 33; Significance to W.D. Davies: Contributor
    - The International Critical Commentary: Matthew (Volume I), 1988 (Box 67)
      Author: W.D. Davies and Dale C. Allison Jr.; Publisher: T&T Clark Limited; Place of Publication: Edinburgh; Hardcover; Language: English; Volume 1 of 3; Significance to W.D. Davies: Co-authored
    - The International Critical Commentary: Matthew (Volume II), 1991 (Box 67)
      Author: W.D. Davies and Dale C. Allison Jr.; Publisher: T&T Clark Limited; Place of Publication: Edinburgh; Hardcover; Language: English; Volume 2 of 3; Significance to W.D. Davies: Co-authored
    - The International Critical Commentary: Matthew (Volume III), 1997 (Box 67)
      Author: W.D. Davies and Dale C. Allison Jr.; Publisher: T&T Clark Limited; Place of Publication: Edinburgh; Hardcover; Language: English; Volume 3 of 3; Significance to W.D. Davies: Co-authored
    - The Interpretation of the New Testament 1981-1961, 1964 (Box 68)
      Author: Stephen Neill; Publisher: The Oxford University Pres; Place of Publication: Oxford; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Annotated
    - Introduction to Pharisaism, 1967 (Box 63)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: Fortress Press; Place of Publication: Philadelphia; Paperback; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - An Introductory Hebrew Grammar, 1930 (Box 64)
      Author: A.B. Davidson; Publisher: Morrison and Gibb; Place of Publication: Great Britain; Hardcover; Language: English; Twenty third edition; Significance to W.D. Davies: Annotated
    - Invitation to the New Testament, 1966 (Box 68)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: Doubleday and Company; Place of Publication: New York; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored, Annotated
    - Invitation to the New Testament: A Guide to Its Main Witness, 1966 (Box 62)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: Doubleday and Company; Place of Publication: New York; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - Israel in Revolution 6-74 CE: A Political History based on the Writings of Josephus, 1976 (Box 66)
      Author: David M. Rhodes; Publisher: Fortress Press; Place of Publication: Philadelphia; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription, Dedication
    - Israel: An Echo of Eternity, 1967 (Box 68)
      Author: Abraham Joshua Heschel; Publisher: Doubleday Canada LTD; Place of Publication: Toronto; Paperback; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Annotated
    - Jesus and Judaism, 1985 (Box 73)
      Author: E.P. Sanders; Publisher: Fortress Press; Place of Publication: Philadelphia; Hardcover; Language: English
    - Jesus of Nazareth: Millenarian Prophet (Box 74)
      Author: Dale C. Allison; Language: English
    - The Jesus Tradition in Q, 1997 (Box 68)
      Author: Dale C. Allison, Jr.; Publisher: Trinity Press International; Place of Publication: Harrisburg, Pennsylvania; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Mentioned in Preface
    - Jewish and Pauline Studies, 1984 (Box 62)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: Fortress Press; Place of Publication: Philadelphia; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - Jewish and Pauline Studies, 1984 (Box 63)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: Fortress Press; Place of Publication: United States; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - Jewish Law From Moses to the Mishnah: From Bible to Torah, 1999 (Box 73)
      Author: Jacob Neusner; Paperback; Language: English
    - Jewish Life and Thought Among Greeks and Romans, 1996 (Box 70)
      Author: Lewis Felman and Meyer Reinhold; Publisher: Fortress Press; Place of Publication: Minneapolis; Paperback; Language: English
    - The Jewish People: History, Religion, Literature, 1973 (Box 63)
      Author: W.D. Davies; Publisher: Arno Press; Place of Publication: New York; Hardcover; Language: English; Reprint of 1962 edition; Significance to W.D. Davies: Authored
    - Jews and Christians: Exploring the Past, Present and Future, 1990 (Box 73)
      Author: James H. Charlesworth; Publisher: Crossroad Publishing Co; Place of Publication: New York; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Jews, Greeks and Christians: Religious Cultures in Late Antiquity: essays in honor of William David Davies, 1976 (Box 65)
      Author: Edited by Robert Hammerton-Kelly and Robin Scroggs; Publisher: Ej Brill; Place of Publication: Netherlands; Hardcover; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: His Feschrift